{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Water Damage Restoration Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40029/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40029,"taskName":"Recovery Service - Water Removal","taskDescription":"Remove Unwanted Water","xmTaskDescriptor":"Water Damage Restoration Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":308,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"recovery water storm hurricane","textMessagingName":"Water Removal Recvry","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically includes both pumping operations as well as dryers.","rolloverShortDesc":"Pump out water from fires, floods, plumbing \u0026 sewer problems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remove Unwanted Water.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Water Damage Restoration \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Water Removal \u0026 Damage Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":63,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Water Removal Recovery","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Recovery Service - Water Removal","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Water Removal Recovery Project","urlName":"Recovery-Service-Water-Removal","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Water Damage Restoration Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Water Removal","searchKeywords":"recovery,water,removal,storm,hurricane,damage,remove,dry,pump,basement,emergency","emcCategoryOid":-12022,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":353,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40029/":{"taskOID":40029,"originalTaskOID":40029,"setID":353,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1565,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Water Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How extensive is the water damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":965,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement is flooded","answerDisplayText":"Basement is flooded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3710,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Main or upper floor is flooded","answerDisplayText":"Main or upper floor is flooded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1161,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Building materials are wet","answerDisplayText":"Building materials are wet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1250,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Carpet and floors are damp","answerDisplayText":"Carpet and floors are damp","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1446,"questionDisplayText":"Time Area has been Wet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long has the area been wet?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 24 hours","answerDisplayText":"Less than 24 hours","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1031,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Between one day and one week","answerDisplayText":"Between one day and one week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3656,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Longer than one week","answerDisplayText":"Longer than one week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3911,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Months","answerDisplayText":"Months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1443,"questionDisplayText":"Cause of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select possible causes of the water damage.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6425,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Toilet overflow","answerDisplayText":"Toilet overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pipe burst","answerDisplayText":"Pipe burst","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fire sprinkler went off","answerDisplayText":"Fire sprinkler went off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink overflow","answerDisplayText":"Sink overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6836,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Washing machine hose","answerDisplayText":"Washing machine hose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drain back-up","answerDisplayText":"Drain back-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5403,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roof leak","answerDisplayText":"Roof leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5808,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","answerDisplayText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1444,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms Affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms in your home are currently being affected by the damage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":272,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 room","answerDisplayText":"1 room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 rooms","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 10 rooms","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2236,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire home","answerDisplayText":"Entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1565,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Water Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How extensive is the water damage? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":965,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement is flooded","answerDisplayText":"Basement is flooded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3710,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Main or upper floor is flooded","answerDisplayText":"Main or upper floor is flooded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1161,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Building materials are wet","answerDisplayText":"Building materials are wet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1250,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Carpet and floors are damp","answerDisplayText":"Carpet and floors are damp","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":965,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement is flooded","answerDisplayText":"Basement is flooded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3710,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Main or upper floor is flooded","answerDisplayText":"Main or upper floor is flooded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1161,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Building materials are wet","answerDisplayText":"Building materials are wet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1250,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Carpet and floors are damp","answerDisplayText":"Carpet and floors are damp","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1446,"questionDisplayText":"Time Area has been Wet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long has the area been wet?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 24 hours","answerDisplayText":"Less than 24 hours","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1031,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Between one day and one week","answerDisplayText":"Between one day and one week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3656,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Longer than one week","answerDisplayText":"Longer than one week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3911,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Months","answerDisplayText":"Months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 24 hours","answerDisplayText":"Less than 24 hours","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1031,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Between one day and one week","answerDisplayText":"Between one day and one week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3656,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Longer than one week","answerDisplayText":"Longer than one week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3911,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Months","answerDisplayText":"Months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1443,"questionDisplayText":"Cause of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select possible causes of the water damage.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6425,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Toilet overflow","answerDisplayText":"Toilet overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pipe burst","answerDisplayText":"Pipe burst","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fire sprinkler went off","answerDisplayText":"Fire sprinkler went off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink overflow","answerDisplayText":"Sink overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6836,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Washing machine hose","answerDisplayText":"Washing machine hose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drain back-up","answerDisplayText":"Drain back-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5403,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roof leak","answerDisplayText":"Roof leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5808,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","answerDisplayText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6425,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Toilet overflow","answerDisplayText":"Toilet overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pipe burst","answerDisplayText":"Pipe burst","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fire sprinkler went off","answerDisplayText":"Fire sprinkler went off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink overflow","answerDisplayText":"Sink overflow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6836,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Washing machine hose","answerDisplayText":"Washing machine hose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Drain back-up","answerDisplayText":"Drain back-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5403,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roof leak","answerDisplayText":"Roof leak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5808,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","answerDisplayText":"Slow or gradual leak or water exposure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1444,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms Affected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms in your home are currently being affected by the damage?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":272,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 room","answerDisplayText":"1 room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 rooms","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 10 rooms","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2236,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire home","answerDisplayText":"Entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":272,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 room","answerDisplayText":"1 room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":364,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 rooms","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":499,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 10 rooms","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2236,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entire home","answerDisplayText":"Entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}